question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                       "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                       "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
